What?
Co?
EPISODE 1
ODCINEK 1
What is this?
Co to ma być?
No!
Nie!
Where... Where am I?
Gdzie ja jestem?
What?
Co?
Memi?
Memi?
Memi!
Memi!
Mirei?
Mirei?
Where are we?
Gdzie my jesteśmy?
I don't know!
Nie wiem!
Hey!
Hej!
Oh, God!
Boże!
I can't take this!
Nie wytrzymam!
What?
Co?
Sarina?
Sarina?
Yes?
Tak?
Sarina!
Sarina!
Mirei!
Mirei!
Hey! Stop it!
Hej! Przestań!
What's going on?
Co tu się dzieje?
What is this?
Co to ma być?
Mao?
Mao?
Where are we?
Co to za miejsce?
How should I know?
Skąd mam wiedzieć?
Mei!
Mei!
Toto?
Toto?
Toto! Where's Toto?
Gdzie jest Toto?
-Toto? -Toto!
- Toto? - Toto!
Tell me where Toto is!
Gdzie ona jest?
Who's Toto?
Kto to?
I was taking her for a walk! Where is she?
Byłam z nią na spacerze. Gdzie jest Toto?
Is that your dog?
To twój pies?
How should I know?
Skąd mam wiedzieć?
Where in the world are we?
Gdzie my jesteśmy?
I'd like to know, too.
Też chciałabym wiedzieć.
Sarina.
Sarina,
What were you doing before you woke up here?
co robiłaś, zanim się tu obudziłaś?
I was on my way home from my job.
Wracałam z pracy.
I unlocked my bicycle
Odpięłam rower...
and then woke up here.
i obudziłam się tutaj.
What about you?
A ty?
I was at home practicing tomorrow's speech.
Byłam w domu, uczyłam się przemowy na jutro.
Right. Graduation is tomorrow.
Racja, mamy zakończenie roku.
But then, I woke up here.
Nagle obudziłam się tutaj.
The last thing I remember is
Ostatnia rzecz, jaką pamiętam,
somebody was speaking to me in a foreign language.
to ktoś mówiący do mnie w obcym języku.
I don't know what language, but they were speaking fast!
Nie wiem w jakim, ale mówił bardzo szybko!
The same thing happened to me!
Ze mną było tak samo!
Really?
Naprawdę?
What? Foreigners? That didn't happen to me.
Co? Obcokrajowiec? Ze mną tak nie było.
Where are we, anyway?
Gdzie my właściwie jesteśmy?
-We don't know! -You don't have to get nasty!
- Nie wiemy! - Nie musisz być niemiła!
Calm down!
Uspokój się!
Ayaka?
Ayaka?
Mei?
Mei?
Don't scare me like that!
Nie strasz mnie!
What is this place?
Co to za miejsce?
Where are we?
Gdzie my jesteśmy?
How should I know? I wish someone would tell me.
Skąd mam wiedzieć? Uwierzcie, bardzo bym chciała.
Help us.
Pomocy.
-Help us. -We just woke up ourselves.
- Pomocy. - Same dopiero się obudziłyśmy.
Help us.
Pomocy.
NO SIGNAL
BRAK SYGNAŁU
All the clocks are wrong.
Zegary pokazują złą godzinę.
Why?
Dlaczego?
It was about five o'clock.
Było koło 17.
-What? -When I last checked the clock.
- Co? - Kiedy ostatni raz sprawdzałam godzinę.
Which means...
To znaczy...
Seven hours. We've been out for seven hours!
Siedem godzin. Byłyśmy nieprzytomne przez siedem godzin!
Were we here the whole time?
Gdzie byłyśmy przez cały ten czas?
You know, everyone here is...
Wiecie, wszystkie tutaj...
What? What's happening, everyone?
Co? Co tu się dzieje?
Where are we?
Gdzie jesteśmy?
I don't know!
Nie wiem!
Stay away!
Uciekaj!
Why doesn't she wake up?
Dlaczego się nie budzi?
How can she sit still when we're all screaming?
Jak może spać, gdy wszystkie wrzeszczymy?
Do you think she's dead?
Myślicie, że nie żyje?
No, no!
Nie!
Quit screaming!
Nie wrzeszcz!
I want to sleep more!
Chcę jeszcze trochę pospać!
Kyoko?
Kyoko?
Kyoko!
Kyoko!
Ayaka?
Ayaka?
What? What is this place?
Co? Co to za miejsce?
Why are we here?
Gdzie my jesteśmy?
You know, aren't we all...
Czy my wszystkie przypadkiem...
Right. We're all in the same class.
Tak, jesteśmy z tej samej klasy.
This room is crazy.
Ten pokój jest dziwaczny.
Where are we, Memi?
Memi, gdzie jesteśmy?
I don't know where we are!
Nie wiem!
This must be a dream.
To musi być sen.
A dream?
Sen?
It's a dream.
To sen.
It's just a dream.
To tylko sen.
I wish it were a dream.
Chciałabym, żeby to był sen.
But...
Ale...
What?
Co?
Dear God, please protect us.
Boże, miej nas w swojej opiece.
If you let one of us live, please let it be me.
Jeśli któraś z nas ma przeżyć, błagam, niech to będę ja.
-please let it be me. -What a bitch!
- proszę, niech to będę ja. - Co za suka!
Please protect us.
Miej nas w swojej opiece.
Please!
Proszę!
This is our last day in high school,
To miał być ostatni dzień liceum.
but why is this happening?
Dlaczego nas to spotkało?
Will this really open these?
Myślisz, że to zadziała?
I don't know, but we have to escape.
Nie wiem, ale musimy uciec.
How's it going, Shiho?
Jak ci idzie, Shiho?
That's dangerous. Cut it out.
To niebezpieczne, przestań.
But, we have to do something.
Musimy coś zrobić.
I wonder if the key is in that dresser.
Może klucz jest w szafce.
Even if it is, we can't reach it.
Nawet jeśli, nie dosięgniemy tam.
Mei, try to think of something, too.
Mei, też coś wymyśl.
There's no way there's a key.
Na pewno nie ma tam klucza.
I'd have to agree. There are a lot of places it could be.
Zgadzam się. Mógłby być wszędzie.
Would whoever did this put a key where we could reach it?
Myślicie, że ktoś by nas tu zamknął, a potem dał nam klucz?
You're right.
Masz rację.
WI-FI CONNECTING...
ŁĄCZENIE Z WI-FI...
UNABLE TO CONNECT
BRAK POŁĄCZENIA
It's useless. There's no signal.
To na nic, nie ma zasięgu.
There might be a Wi-Fi signal.
Może złapię Wi-Fi.
We need to call for help.
Musimy wezwać pomoc.
Where the hell are we?
Gdzie my, do cholery, jesteśmy?
Isn't our seating arrangement the same as last time?
Nie siedzimy przypadkiem tak jak ostatnio?
What? When?
Co? Kiedy?
I can't remember.
Nie pamiętam.
I do remember seeing Mei, Sarina, and Mirei sitting in that order.
Pamiętam, że Mei, Sarina i Mirei siedziały w takiej kolejności.
Then...
Tylko...
who was in that seat?
kto siedział tam?
I wonder if they're in there.
Ciekawe, czy tu jest.
Who?
Kto?
Whoever locked us in here.
Ten, kto nas tu zamknął.
Then we'd better escape before they come back.
Lepiej ucieknijmy, zanim wróci.
What's wrong, Sarina?
O co chodzi, Sarina?
-That chair. -What about it?
- To krzesło. - Co z nim?
All of us here are from Class Two.
Wszystkie jesteśmy z klasy B.
-Yeah. -But not everyone is here.
- Tak. - Ale nie ma tu całej klasy.
You're right.
To prawda.
In our class...
W naszej klasie...
there are 20 of us.
jest 20 osób.
There are...
Tu mamy...
One, two, three, four, five,
Raz, dwa, trzy, cztery,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven.
pięć, sześć, siedem, osiem, dziewięć, dziesięć, jedenaście.
Why are there just us?
Czemu tylko my?
-That's not... -Be quiet!
- To nie... - Cicho!
Who would be there?
Kto tu jest?
Hey, Memi.
Hej, Memi.
Weren't all of us...
Czy my wszystkie...
Yes.
Tak.
That's where Miho sat.
Tam siedziała Miho.
But, three months ago, Miho...
Ale trzy miesiące temu Miho...
That's what I can't understand.
Właśnie. Dlatego nie rozumiem.
Where did it go?
Gdzie on zniknął?
A huge rat ran that way!
Tam pobiegł wielki szczur!
Go back!
Wracaj!
Go away!
Uciekaj!
I can't take this! I don't want to die here!
Nie wytrzymam! Nie chcę tu umrzeć!
I don't want to die!
Nie chcę umierać!
That's the last thing anyone wants to hear right now!
To ostatnia rzecz, jakiej chcemy teraz słuchać.
Sorry.
Przepraszam.
The only thing we can do now is to destroy the floor.
Nie pozostaje nam nic innego jak zniszczyć podłogę.
The floor?
Podłogę?
How?
Jak?
We can't remove the leg-irons,
Nie zdejmiemy tych kajdan,
but if we break the floor under them, then we can escape, right?
ale jeśli rozwalimy podłogę pod nimi, uciekniemy.
One person can't do it,
Jednej osobie się nie uda,
but if we lift our legs all together, we might be able to.
ale jeśli podniesiemy nogi równocześnie, może damy radę.
The whole floor?
Całą podłogę?
I think it's impossible, but...
Myślę, że to niemożliwe, ale...
It's times like this...
W takich chwilach...
that we need to trust our class rep!
musimy zaufać naszej przewodniczącej!
Let's all do it.
Do dzieła.
Let's try.
Spróbujmy.
Mei?
Mei?
Mei! Wake up, Mei!
Mei! Obudź się!
-Mei! -That's enough. Forget about her.
- Mei! - Dobra, zostaw ją.
She can stay here.
Może tu zostać.
No! I'll do it.
Nie, zrobię to!
When I give the signal, lift your legs together.
Na mój znak wszystkie podnosimy nogi.
Use all your strength.
Uderzcie z całej siły.
Ready, go!
Gotowe, start!
What's wrong?
O co chodzi?
That armor moved just now!
Ta zbroja się poruszyła.
Don't say stuff like that, Mao.
Nie mów takich rzeczy, Mao.
I'm serious! The eye holes were shaking.
Naprawdę! Otwory na oczy się zatrzęsły.
Shut up!
Cicho!
Okay, let's do it.
Dobrze. Do roboty.
Ready, go!
Gotowe, start!
-It hurts! -Are you okay?
- To boli! - W porządku?
I'm all right.
Tak.
Keep going.
Dalej.
Next, let's do it several times in a row.
Zróbmy to kilka razy z rzędu.
Let's do it five times in a row with all our strength.
Pięć razy z całej siły.
Mao!
Mao!
Sorry.
Przepraszam.
Okay, here goes.
Dobrze, teraz.
Ready, go! One!
Gotowe, start! Raz!
Two! Three!
Dwa! Trzy!
Four!
Cztery!
See! I told you it was dangerous!
Mówiłam, że to niebezpieczne!
What's that?
Co to jest?
A clock?
Zegar?
Mirei?
Mirei?
Are you okay, Mirei?
Wszystko w porządku? Mirei?
I'm getting a really bad feeling.
Mam złe przeczucia.
About what?
Odnośnie czego?
I don't know, but I'm getting a bad premonition.
Nie wiem, ale czuję, że stanie się coś złego.
Quit saying those things!
Przestań tak mówić!
-What? -Something just moved!
- Co? - Coś się poruszyło!
-It was a mouse. -No, it was bigger!
- Mysz. - Nie, coś większego!
What did you see?
Co widziałaś?
Believe me! It was bigger than that!
Uwierzcie, że było większe!
Damn you! Quit scaring us like that!
Niech cię szlag! Przestań nas straszyć!
I know!
Wiem!
I remember now!
Pamiętam!
-What? -You remember what?
- Co? - Co pamiętasz?
This seating arrangement.
To, jak siedziałyśmy.
Here it is! Look!
Znalazłam! Patrzcie!
-What's going on? -What is it?
- Co się dzieje? - Co jest?
What is it?
Co się stało?
A blackout... Maybe?
Może prąd wysiadł?
Mao?
Mao?
This is insane.
To jakieś szaleństwo.
She's gone.
Zniknęła.
You're kidding!
Żartujesz!
I can't take this!
Nie wytrzymam!
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION.
PRZEDSTAWIONY SERIAL JEST FIKCJĄ.
Subtitle translation by Brian Athey
Napisy: Arianna Sugier